1. JobScheduler and JobServices
	compared to using AlarmManager, IntentService and PendingIntents together
		JobScheduler allows you to define services to run particular jobs, and then schedule them to run only when particular conditions apply.
	introduced in Lollipop (API 22)
	to use
		subclass JobService to create a service to handle your job
			onStartJob(JobParameters)
				when the system matches the conditions you set to run your service, a call to onStartJob will be performed on your main thread
				return false means "job completed"
					return true means "still working on this job"
				since it's called on the main thread, you are expected to do your own threading
					unlike IntentService
			
			jobFinished(JobParameters, boolean)
				when you're done with your job, call jobFinished()
				passing true for the second parameter means that you were not able to get the job done this time,
					and that the job should be rescheduled again for the future

			onStopJob(JobParameters)
				called when your job needs to be interrupt, telling you to drop everything immediately, no waiting is allowed
					e.g. the conditions aren't satisfied any more before you call jobFinished()
				Returning true means that your job should be rescheduled to run again in the future

			sample code
				public class PollService extends JobService {				
					private PollTask mCurrentTask;

					@Override
					public boolean onStartJob(JobParameters params) {
					    mCurrentTask = new PollTask();
					    mCurrentTask.execute(params);
					    return true;
					}

					private class PollTask extends AsyncTask<JobParameters,Void,Void> {
					    @Override
					    protected Void doInBackground(JobParameters... params) {
						JobParameters jobParams = params[0];

						// Poll Flickr for new images

						jobFinished(jobParams, false);
						return null;
					    }
					}

					@Override
					public boolean onStopJob(JobParameters params) {
					    if (mCurrentTask != null) {
						mCurrentTask.cancel(true);
					    }
					    return true;
					}
				}

		register the service in the manifest
			<service
				android:name=".PollService"
				android:permission="android.permission.BIND_JOB_SERVICE"
				android:exported="true"/>
			Exporting it exposes it to the world at large, but adding the permission restricts it back down so that only JobScheduler can run it
		
		use JobScheduler
			check whether the job has been scheduled
				final int JOB_ID = 1;

				JobScheduler scheduler = (JobScheduler)
				    context.getSystemService(Context.JOB_SCHEDULER_SERVICE);

				boolean hasBeenScheduled = false;
				for (JobInfo jobInfo : scheduler.getAllPendingJobs()) {
				    if (jobInfo.getId() == JOB_ID) {
					hasBeenScheduled = true;
				    }
				}
			run the service
				final int JOB_ID = 1;

				JobScheduler scheduler = (JobScheduler)
				    context.getSystemService(Context.JOB_SCHEDULER_SERVICE);

				JobInfo jobInfo = new JobInfo.Builder(
					JOB_ID, new ComponentName(context, PollService.class))
					.setRequiredNetworkType(JobInfo.NETWORK_TYPE_UNMETERED)
					.setPeriodic(1000 * 60 * 15)
					.setPersisted(true)		// it will survive a reboot
					.build();
				scheduler.schedule(jobInfo);

2. Sync Adapters  --another way to set up a regularly polling web service
	its sole purpose is to sync data with a data source (uploading, downloading, or both)
		Syncs from multiple applications are grouped together by default
	Sync adapters also integrate nicely with the OS from a user perspective. 
		You can expose your app as a sync-able account that the user can manage through the Settings -> Accounts menu
		Google's suite of apps use sync adapters
	but implementation is relatively complicated

3. broadcast intents
	why?
		to run the service even if the user has not opened the app since booting the device
		to ensure notifications are posted only if the user is not interacting with the app
	broadcast intents can be received by multiple components, called broadcast receivers, at the same time
	broadcast receiver
		just like a service or an activity
		standalone receiver
			a broadcast receiver that is declared in the manifest. 
				Such a receiver can be activated even if your app process is dead
				Your process came to life just long enough to run your broadcast receiver, and then it died again after done onReceive(Context, Intent)

		broadcast receivers' short lives restrict the things you can do with them
			you cannot use any asunchronous api
			you cannot register any listeners, since the receiver will not be alive after onReceive()
			you cannot do any heavy lifting, such as networking or heavy works with permanent storage
				since onReceive() runs on the main thread of the process
		instead, via receivers, you start an activity or a service,
			or you reset a recurring alarm

4. to use broadcast intents
	to wake the service up on boot
		listen to a BOOT_COMPLETED broadcast intent sent by the system, using a standalone receiver
		how?
			create a broadcast receiver
				public class StartupReceiver extends BroadcastReceiver{
				    private static final String TAG = "StartupReceiver";

				    @Override
				    public void onReceive(Context context, Intent intent) {
					Log.i(TAG, "Received broadcast intent: " + intent.getAction());

					boolean isOn = QueryPreferences.isAlarmOn(context);	// you use shared preference to save the status of the alarm
				        PollService.setServiceAlarm(context, isOn);		// start an alarm
				    }
				}
			register it as a standalone receiver
				<manifest ...>

				    <uses-permission android:name="android.permission.RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED" />

				    <application
					...>
					<receiver android:name=".StartupReceiver">
					    <intent-filter>
						<action android:name="android.intent.action.BOOT_COMPLETED"/>
					    </intent-filter>
					</receiver>
				    </application>

				</manifest>

Filtering Foreground Notifications
