1. two ways to browse the web
	use implicit intents to work with the device's browser app
		Intent i = new Intent(Intent.ACTION_VIEW, uri_here);

	use WebView
		make a space for WebView in the layout
		get the WebView in the fragment, configure it and load the url
			mWebView.getSettings().setJavaScriptEnabled(true);	// enable JavaScript if necessary
				// get an instance of WebSettings via getSettings()
				// ebSettings is the first of the three ways you can modify your WebView. 
				// It has various properties you can set, like the user agent string and text size.

			mWebView.setWebViewClient(new WebViewClient() {		// by providing your own implementation of WebViewClient, you can respond to rendering events
			    public boolean shouldOverrideUrlLoading(WebView view, String url) {
				// this method determines what happens when a new URL is loading in the WebView
				// for example when you click a link, or simply an automatic redirect to the mobile version of the website
				// by default, it fires an implicit intent with the URL
				// to avoid being sent to a web browser web, you override this method to do nothing but returning a boolean
					// returning true means you will handle the URL, so the WebView will do nothing
					// returning false asks the WebView to load the URL
				return false;
			    }
			});
			mWebView.loadUrl(mUri.toString());			// Loading the URL has to be done after configuring the WebView

		using WebChromeClient to implement a progress bar and update the toolbar's subtitle to be the title of the web page
			add a progress bar into the layout
				<RelativeLayout ...>

				    <ProgressBar
					android:id="@+id/fragment_photo_page_progress_bar"
					android:layout_width="match_parent"
					android:layout_height="wrap_content"
					android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
					android:visibility="gone"	// this view is invisible, and does not take any space for layout purposes
									// "invisible": invisible, but still takes out space
					style="?android:attr/progressBarStyleHorizontal"
					android:background="?attr/colorPrimary"/>

				    <WebView
					android:id="@+id/fragment_photo_page_web_view"
					android:layout_width="match_parent"
					android:layout_height="match_parent"
					android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
					android:layout_below="@id/fragment_photo_page_progress_bar" />

				</RelativeLayout>
			
			get the progress bar
				mProgressBar = (ProgressBar)v.findViewById(R.id.fragment_photo_page_progress_bar);
				mProgressBar.setMax(100); // WebChromeClient reports in range 0-100

			set the WebChromeClient
				// WebChromeClient is an event interface for reacting to events that should change elements of chrome around the browser

				mWebView.setWebChromeClient(new WebChromeClient() {
				    public void onProgressChanged(WebView webView, int newProgress) {
					if (newProgress == 100) {
					    mProgressBar.setVisibility(View.GONE);	// it's gone!!
					} else {
					    mProgressBar.setVisibility(View.VISIBLE);
					    mProgressBar.setProgress(newProgress);
					}
				    }

				    public void onReceivedTitle(WebView webView, String title) {
					AppCompatActivity activity = (AppCompatActivity) getActivity();
					activity.getSupportActionBar().setSubtitle(title);
				    }
				});
		
		proper rotation with WebView
			some views will still be destroyed and recreated even if the underlying fragment is retained
				such as WebView and VideoView
				for these views, the Android documentation recommends that you allow the activity to handle the configuration change itself
					it simply moves its views around to fit the new screen size	
			how?
				<activity
					  android:name=".PhotoPageActivity"
					  android:configChanges="keyboardHidden|orientation|screenSize" />

			dangers of doing this
				resource qualifiers no longer work automatically
				and death and re-creation in low-memory situations should still be considered
			so usually we just use this approach for this kind of views

2. more about WebView
	injecting JavaScript object
		create an object in WebView that can be access via JavaScript in the web page
		how?
			create an object
				mWebView.addJavascriptInterface(new Object() {
				    @JavascriptInterface	// only public methods with this annotation will be exported to JavaScript
				    public void send(String message) {
					Log.i(TAG, "Received message: " + message);
				    }
				}, "androidObject");		// this is the name of this object
			
			access it in the web page
				<script type="text/javascript">
				    function sendToAndroid(message) {
					androidObject.send(message);
				    }
				</script>
		
		could be dangerous, since you are letting some potentially strange web page fiddle with your program
			to be safe, make sure you own the HTML
				or, be extremely conservative with the interface you expose
	
	WebView since KitKat (4.4, API 19)
		based on the Chromium open source project
			shares the same rendering engine used by the Chrome for Android app
		so there are many improvements
			support for new web standards like CSS3 and HTML5
			support for remote debugging of WebView using Chrome DevTools 
				which can be enabled by calling WebView.setWebContentsDebuggingEnabled()

		to learn more about differences between pre- and post-KitKat versions of WebView
			 http://​developer.android.com/​guide/​webapps/​migrating.html

	use the back button for browser history
		by default, when you press the back button, it goes back to the last task
		to go back to the last web page
			override the back button method Activity.onBackPressed()
				use WebView.canGoBack() and WebView.goBack() to check if there's browing history and go back to the previous item
				it there's no browsing history, super.onBackPressed()
	
	supporting non-HTTP links
		WebView cannot load non-HTTP links, so you should not always return false in shouldOverrideUrlLoading()
			instead, you check the scheme, if it's not HTTP or HTTPS, issue an Intent.ACTION_VIEW for it
	