1. master-detail interface (two-pane layout)	--usually for tablet
	create a layout for two panes (some attributes are omitted)
		<LinearLayout android:divider="?android:attr/dividerHorizontal"		// show the divider
			      android:showDividers="middle">				// the ? notation says to use the resource that dividerHorizontal attributepoints to
		    <FrameLayout
			android:id="@+id/fragment_container"
			android:layout_width="0dp"
			android:layout_weight="1"></FrameLayout>			// 1:3 width

		    <FrameLayout
			android:id="@+id/detail_fragment_container"
			android:layout_width="0dp"
			android:layout_weight="3"></FrameLayout>
		</LinearLayout>
	alias resource
		a resource that points to another resource
		res/values/refs.xml
			you create an alias resource points to one layout
			and then another alias resource with a qualifier points to another layout
			actually it has the same function as you creating a layout with the same name, and with a qualifier
		in refs.xml
			<resources>	
			  <item name="activity_masterdetail" type="layout">@layout/activity_fragment</item>
			</resources>
			// the item will have a ID: R.layout.activity_masterdetail
		in refs.xml with a qualifier of Smallest Screen Width of 600dp		// Smallest Screen Width refers to the smallest dimension of a device
											// independent of the device's current orientation
			<resources>	
			  <item name="activity_masterdetail" type="layout">@layout/activity_twopane</item>
			</resources>
			// has the same ID
	inflate the alias layout, i.e,, R.layout.activity_masterdetail, in your activity
		Android will determine which layout to use based on the qualifier
	callbacks
		one fragment may want to talk to the other one
			e.g. clicking an item in the master creates a detail, or modifying the detail updates the master
		if you get the hosting activity and its fragmentManager to create a detail fragment,
			your fragment is no longer a standalone, composable unit
		instead, you talk to the hosting activity using callbacks, and let it deal with it
		to implement it
			define an interface in the fragment, containing a method can be called by the fragment
				every activity hosts this fragment "must" implement it
				actually the "must" is no guarunteed, just in documentation
				    /**
				     * Required interface for hosting activities.
				     */
				    public interface Callbacks {
					void onCrimeSelected(Crime crime);
				    }
			keep the hosting activity in the fragment
				    private Callbacks mCallbacks;

				    @Override			// called when a fragment is attached to an activity
				    public void onAttach(Activity activity) {	// actually, this method is deprecated
					super.onAttach(activity);		// the newer API uses onAttach(Context)
										// but deprecated does not mean not in use
										// but we use the deprecated one for compatibility
					mCallbacks = (Callbacks) activity;
				    }
				    @Override
				    public void onDetach() {
					super.onDetach();
					mCallbacks = null;
				    }
			implements the interface in the hosting Activity
			call the callback method in fragment when it's necessary
	in the hosting activity, to determine which layout is in use
		check if the components uniquely exist in a layout already exist
			e.g. here, R.id.detail_fragment_container is in activity_twopane layout, not in activity_fragment layout
			    if (findViewById(R.id.detail_fragment_container) == null) {
				Intent intent = CrimePagerActivity.newIntent(this, crime.getId());
				startActivity(intent);
			    } else {
				Fragment newDetail = CrimeFragment.newInstance(crime.getId());

				getSupportFragmentManager().beginTransaction()
					.replace(R.id.detail_fragment_container, newDetail)	// replace the detail fragemnt !
					.commit();
			    }
	
2. tips
	in the fragment, list the overriden lifecycle method in the exact order they happen!
	which is:
		fragment added -onAttach()-> -onCreate()-> -onCreateView()-> -onActivityCreated()-> -onStart()-> -onResume-> fragment active
		user navigates back or fragment is removed/replaced -onPause()-> -onStop()-> onDestroyView()
			fragment returns to the layout from the back stack -onCreateView()-> ...
			-onDestoy()-> -onDetach()-> fragment destroyed
			or, if retained, -onDetach()-> -onAttach()-> -onCreateView()-> ...

3. screen dimensional qualifiers
	wXXXdp	Available width: width is greater than or equal to XXX dp
	hXXXdp	Available height: height greater than or equal to XXX dp
	swXXXdp	Smallest width: width or height (whichever is smaller) greater than or equal to XXX dp
		the first two are dependent on the current orientation

4. assets
	a little file system that ships with your packaged application
	commonly used for loading graphics and sound in applications that have a lot of those things, like games
	the reason to use assets instead of resources
		to store files in resource, all you can do is store them in res/raw
		there's no way to organize them
		if you have a large amount of files, it will be a mess

	use it
		import assets
			create an asset folder, by right click Java, then New → Folder → Assets Folder
			you can create any directory in the asset folder to manage your assets
			copy your resources to the folder, (right click and show in explorer)
		get at assets
			assets are accessed via AssetManager, which can be fetched from any Context
				don't have to worry about what Context to use, every Context’s AssetManager will be wired up to the same set of assets
				AssetManager assets = getActivity().getAssets();
			use String[] AssetManager.list(String directoryName) to list all the files in a directory
	access assets
		also use AssetManager to fetch them
			InputStream soundData = mAssets.open(assetPath);	//mAssets is a AssetManager
				// assetPath contains the whole path of the file from the root of assets folder
		some APIs require FileDesriptors (originally from Unix, represents a file or an input/output source), you can get it by:
			AssetFileDescriptor assetFd = mAssets.openFd(assetPath);
			FileDescriptor fd = assetFd.getFileDescriptor();
		
5. SoundPool
	can load a large set of sounds into memory and control the maximum number of sounds that are playing back at any one time
	create a SoundPool
		mSoundPool = new SoundPool(5, AudioManager.STREAM_MUSIC, 0);
			actually this constructor is deprecated, the newer API uses SoundPool.Builder to create a SoundPool
			but we use it for compatibility
		if you try to play a sixth one, the oldest one will stop playing
		the second parameter determines the kind of audio stream your SoundPool will play on
			Android has a variety of different audio streams, each of which has its own independent volume settings
				STREAM_ALARM		The audio stream for alarms
				STREAM_DTMF		The audio stream for DTMF Tones (sounds of dialing)
				STREAM_MUSIC		The audio stream for music playback
				STREAM_NOTIFICATION	The audio stream for notifications
				STREAM_RING		The audio stream for the phone ring
				STREAM_SYSTEM		The audio stream for system sounds
				STREAM_VOICE_CALL	The audio stream for phone calls
		the third parameter is ignored, according to the document, just pass a 0
	load sounds
		SoundPool is responsive, which means there's no lag when playing a sound
			but require loading sounds before playing
		code
			AssetFileDescriptor afd = mAssets.openFd(sound.getAssetPath());
			int soundId = mSoundPool.load(afd, 1);		// returns an ID 
				the second parameter is priority
				tip: you keep the ID in an Integer field, in this way it can have the null state when unavailable
	play sounds
		check the id to see if it's null, this happens when loading fails
		SoundPool.play(int, float, float, int, int, float)
			the sound ID
			volume on the left		1.0 for full volume
			volume on the right
			priority (which is ignored)
			whether the audio should loop	0 for no looping, -1 for forever looping
			playback rate			1.0 for normal
	unload sounds
		when you are done, call SoundPool.release()
			for example, in the fragemnt's onDestroy() method

